https://www.certifiedgoldexchange.com/privacy-policy.php

HomePrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyCertified Gold Exchange, Inc. (www.CertifiedGoldExchange.com) Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy sets out how Certified Gold Exchange, Inc. (www.CertifiedGoldExchange.com) uses and protects any and all information that you may provide to Certified Gold Exchange, Inc. (www.CertifiedGoldExchange.com) when you use our website.Certified Gold Exchange, Inc. (www.CertifiedGoldExchange.com) is committed to ensuring that your privacy is sufficiently legally protected. If we ask you to provide information by which you could be identified when using our website, then you can rest assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement, as Certified Gold Exchange, Inc. (www.CertifiedGoldExchange.com) is known as “America’s Trusted Source For Gold.”Certified Gold Exchange, Inc. (www.CertifiedGoldExchange.com) may change our privacy policy by updating this page. You should check this page occasionally to ensure that you understand and agree with any changes. Our current privacy policy is effective from December 30, 2014.What we collectWe may collect the following types of information:NameContact information including email addressDemographic information such as zip codeInformation relevant to customer surveys and/or special discount offersWhat we do with the information we gatherWe require this information to better understand your needs and provide you with a higher quality service.Particularly, it’s for the following reasons:Internal record keepingImproving our products and servicesSending periodic promotional emails about new products, special offers or other types of information which we think you may find valuableSending you our free and 100% guaranteed 12 Day Investor Safety Educational Email Course so that you can learn strategies to protect your wealth. Contacting you by email, phone, fax or mailCustomizing our website to tailor it to your needs and interestsWe will never sell or share your information. SecurityWe are completely committed to making sure that your information is safe, secure, and protected. In order to prevent unauthorized access to or disclosure of your information, we have put in place various physical, electronic, and managerial procedures for handling personally identifying information.Cookies and how we use themA cookie is a small electronic file that asks for your permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Agreeing to “cookies” means the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic and/or lets you know when you visit a particular website. These cookies allow web applications and websites to respond to you as an individual website user.We use cookies to identify which pages are being used by our website visitors. This helps us analyze data about website/web page traffic and improve this website to tailor it to your needs. We ONLY use this information for statistical and analytical purposes, after which the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Many web browsers automatically accept cookies. However, it is possible to modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you so choose.Children’s PrivacyOur website is intended for use by a general audience and does not offer services to children under the age of 18. If a child whom we suspect to be 17 or younger sends personal information to us, we will use that information only to respond directly to that child to inform him or her that they cannot use this website.Analytics ProgramsOur website uses Google & Bing Analytics as well as Luckyorange to collect information about you and your behaviors. If you would like to opt out of Google Analytics, please visit: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/ and for Bing please visit https://about.ads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/opt-out-of-the-microsoft-advertising-optimization-program and finally from Luckyorange, here is the opt out link https://privacy.luckyorange.com/. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of our website.Links to other websitesOur website may contain links that enable you to visit other websites. However, once you leave our site, understand that we do not have ANY control over that other website, its cookies, information collection practices, etc., and we cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of your information whilst visiting such sites. In these cases, you should read, understand, and agree to the Privacy Policy (or similar page) of that website.Controlling your personal informationYou may choose to restrict our collection or use of your personal information by contacting us directly via the information found on the Contact Us page of this website, and stating to us explicitly that you do not consent to Certified Gold Exchange, Inc. (www.CertifiedGoldExchange.com) holding your personally identifying information.We will not sell, distribute, or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held about you, please write to: Certified Gold Exchange, Inc.
420 Throckmorton St., Suite 210
Fort Worth, TX 76102.If you believe that any information we have about you is incorrect and/or incomplete, please let us know as soon as possible via the contact methods outlined on the Contact Us page of our website. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect and inform you that said changes have been made.If you have any questions, comments, suggestions, etc. about our Certified Gold Exchange, Inc. (www.CertifiedGoldExchange.com) Privacy Policy please contact us directly by emailing: Support@CertifiedGoldExchange. com or by calling us toll-free at(800) 300-0715 now.
SubscribeJoin 75,000 of the most informed investors in the metals market
Email *
Free Gold IRA Kitand 7 Blunders Report
Knowledge is Power! Get Your Free Gold IRA Kit & 7 Blunders Report Now
Get My Gold IRA Kit & 7 Blunders Report
xGet Our Award Winning Reports
Privacy Assurance Policy
Get My Free Reports
Privacy Assurance Policy
$500 Cash Rebate Program on Select US Mint ProductsFund your gold IRA by 9/1/2015 and you'll receive up to $500 cash back.Callers receive expedited service and a free CGE golf cap.Call 1-800-300-0715
No thanks Successfully Submitted!
One Moment
While Your
Requested Guide Is Uploaded.0%
Please Select Your Free Award Winning Publications:
7 Costly Gold & Silver Blunders
Real Money Magazine
Join More Than 75,000 Investors That Have Trusted CGE as Their Source For Metals Information Since 1992
* indicates required fieldFast, Free and Confidential Privacy Assurance Policy100% of our website is encrypted and we never share your info!Paul David VanCleef VP Client ServicesDue to Insurance and Bonding regulations, the Certified Gold Exchange only permits visitor appointments for our institutional investors who meet the following requirements:Current assets invested at CGE of over $2 millionNo state or federal felony convictions3-day advance reservationValid US ID or passportTo set up your visit, please call 1800-300-0715 Ext. 303
xInvestor ToolsPlease choose the following info
Super Cycle
AF
Stocks
Bail-Ins
FDIC
MyRA
US Debt clock.org
Best time to call *
Please Call Now10:00 AM CST11:00 AM CST12:00 PM CST1:00 PM CST2:00 PM CST3:00 PM CST4:00 PM CST5:00 PM CST6:00 PM CST
Receive a Call Now
Privacy Assurance Policy
This CGE website uses cookies for analytics and to personalize content. If you continue to browse our site, you agree that you have read and understand our Privacy Policy.Ok, got itPrivacy policy
